

# **Dzmitry** Karatayeu











# **Front-End Developer**

#### **Profile**

I'm 25 years old Front-End developer based in Minsk with experience in creating SPA using React, Redux, Typescript, HTML, CSS, JS. I improve my skills and expand them with new technologies. Also, I'm studying Node.is because my next focus is to become a Full-Stack Developer.

#### Contacts



**+375 29 871 28 86** 



□ dmitrykorotaev.job@gmail.com



Minsk, Belarus

# **Skill Highlights**

- React/Redux
- JavaScript/TypeScript
- Axios/REST api/Postman
- TDD/Jest/Storybook
- React-hook-form/Formik
- MaterialUI/Ant Design
- HTML, CSS, SCSS
- Git

# Languages

English - Intermediate Russian - Native

# **Work Experience**

#### **Web Developer**

Sep 2021 - Present

#### Part time | Minsk, Belarus

- React development using redux, react-redux, react-routerdom, redux-thunk, axios, formik, ant-design libraries.
- Work with Hooks, TypeScript
- Refactoring, bug fixing, registration and login form creation
- Reusable components development
- Work in a team using Git

# **Acting System Administrator** & Boiler building master

Sep 2019 - Sep 2021

#### Housing and utilities | Logoisk, Belarus

- Performed two jobs at the same time
- Control the operations of the facility
- Updating the 1C system, maintaining the software
- IT support officer for the personnel

### **Education**

# IT-INCUBATOR, Front-End | Minsk, Belarus

2022

Front-end developer with teamwork experience in creating applications by using React, Redux, TypeScript, Axios and other technologies

#### Polotsk State University | Polotsk, Belarus

2014 - 2019

Faculty of Heat, Water, Air and Gas Supply, Civil engineer

#### Polotsk State University | Polotsk, Belarus

2017 - 2019

Faculty of Finance and Economics, Production manager